https://www.joysnamesgifts.com/privacy

07 5599 3844
My Account
Register
Login
Wish List (0)
Show All Rosettes, Sports Medals, Sports Ribbons
Academic, Graduation, Knowledge, Debating, Achievement Trophies & Medals
Achievement Trophies & Medals
Academic Graduation, Knowledge, Debating Trophies & Medals
Show All Academic, Graduation, Knowledge, Debating, Achievement Trophies & Medals
Corporate Awards, Glass & Acrylic, Perpetual Trophies, Cups & Plaques
Corporate Awards, Glass & Acrylic Trophies & Cups
Perpetual Trophies, Cups & Plaques
Trophy Cups
Trophy Plaques
Show All Corporate Awards, Glass & Acrylic, Perpetual Trophies, Cups & Plaques
Custom Badges, Coins, Key Rings, Belt Buckles, Tea Spoons & Medals
Custom Key Rings
Show All Custom Badges, Coins, Key Rings, Belt Buckles, Tea Spoons & Medals
Rosettes, Sports Medals, Sports Ribbons
Academic, Graduation, Knowledge, Debating, Achievement Trophies & Medals
Corporate Awards, Glass & Acrylic, Perpetual Trophies, Cups & Plaques
Custom Badges, Coins, Key Rings, Belt Buckles, Tea Spoons & Medals
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Joys Names Trophies uses and
protects any information that you give Joys Names Trophies when you use
this website.Joys Names Trophies is committed to ensuring
that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain
information by which you can be identified when using this website, then
you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this
privacy statement.Joys Names Trophies may change this policy
from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from
time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.What we collectWe may collect the following information:namecontact information including email addressdemographic information such as postcode, preferences and interestsother information relevant to customer serviceWhat we do with the information we gatherWe
require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a
better service, and in particular for the following reasons:Internal record keeping.We may use the information to improve our products and services.We
may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special
offers or other information which we think you may find interesting
using the email address which you have provided. From time to
time, we may also use your information to contact you for market
research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We
may use the information to customise the website according to your
interests.SecurityWe are committed
to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent
unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable
physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure
the information we collect online.How we use cookiesA
cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your
computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie
helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular
site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual.
The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and
dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your
preferences.We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages
are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and
improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use
this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is
removed from the system.Overall, cookies help us provide you
with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find
useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your
computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to
share with us.You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most
web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify
your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent
you from taking full advantage of the website.Links to other websitesOur
website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once
you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do
not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be
responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you
provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by
this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the
privacy statement applicable to the website in question.Controlling your personal informationWe
will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third
parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.
We may use your personal information to send you promotional information
about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell
us that you wish this to happen.You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998.If
you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or
incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the
above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be
incorrect.
